Partial Solidify
Using Marvelous Designer 11, you can use the select grid brush tool to shape the area on the clothing.
Switch to the select grid brush tool, hold down the left key and drag the mouse to select the area that needs shaping.
Hold down the left key and drag the mouse to select the area that needs shaping.
Once you have finished shaping the area, right-click on the selected grid area and select Shape Shaping.
You can see that the color of the highlight area has changed, which means that this part of the grid has been shaped.
Once the shape is shaped, the grid area will be simulated.
After shaping, the grid area will be simulated.
Once the shape is modeled, the grid area will be vaulted back when the shape is formatted.
In the shape formulation area, right-click, you can select thesplash shape simulation area in the Philos plates,
omas Vil Pres 1949.
Togies
Using the selection moves天使用选择移动工具时该弹出菜单
Manage the splashes of exhausting materials
Once the selected shape is solidified and the area is deleted, the area simulation will return to the previous shape.